{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Simpson_Woodward",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/givenName",
    "object": "Robert Simpson",
    "human_readable": "The given name of Robert Woodward is Robert Simpson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9804233312606812,
            "question": "Could someone named Robert Woodward also be called Robert Simpson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9767765998840332,
            "question": "Is 'Robert Simpson' an alias for someone named Robert Woodward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9688739776611328,
            "question": "Is Robert Simpson a common nickname for Robert Woodward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9437699913978577,
            "question": "What is Robert Woodward's given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.916047990322113,
            "question": "What is the full name of the person often referred to as Robert Woodward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8702031970024109,
            "question": "If someone called Robert Woodward, what other name might they also be known by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8175833821296692,
            "question": "What is Robert Simpson's other name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8159236907958984,
            "question": "Does Robert Woodward have a different name he uses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7945524454116821,
            "question": "What is the alternative name for Robert Woodward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6929100155830383,
            "question": "How many names does Robert Woodward go by?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The given name of Robert Woodward is Robert Simpson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1727_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the alternative name for Robert Woodward?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1727_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Robert Woodward have a different name he uses?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1727_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Robert Simpson's other name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1727_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1727_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provided contain information about Robert Simpson Woodward, including his full name and birthdate. However, there are multiple documents with information about different people named Robert Woodward, which could be confusing. Nevertheless, based on the provided context, it can be inferred that the triple is correct, as all the documents mention a person named Robert Simpson Woodward."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Robert Woodward, including his full name as Robert Simpson Woodward. Therefore, the statement that the given name of Robert Woodward is Robert Simpson is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}